Local changes  uncommitted workspace changes  +375 -10
/ watch
WatchConfigListeningJob.java +17 -1
PublicRecordWatchConfigProces~ +19 -2
WatchConfigListeningJobTest.j~ +50 -0
PublicRecordWatchConfigProces~ +35 -4
old  WatchConfigListeningJob.java                       new  WatchConfigListeningJob.java
- import com.ontic.utils.common.LogUtil;
+ @Mock
+ private WatchConfigProcessor publicRecordProcessor;
q quit    m modes    / search    esc clear search    j/k move    enter diff
Local changes  uncommitted workspace changes  +375 -10
/ mock
17/27
old  WatchConfigListeningJobTest.java                  new  WatchConfigListeningJobTest.java
25     @Mock                                      31     @Mock
26 private WatchConfigProcessor processor;         32 private WatchConfigProcessor processor;
45     when(mockService.execute()).thenReturn(true);
+  @Mock
+  private WatchConfigProcessor publicRecordProcessor;
q quit    m modes    / search    n next    N prev    esc clear search    h/l scroll